EDITH WANJA WANJOHI

Customer Service Representative

Email: eddythwanjohi254@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/wanjohi-wanja

Tel: +254 792 539 124 Address: Nairobi -Kenya

Profile Summary

Dedicated customer service with 5 years of experience providing exceptional customer service, maintaining high level of professionalism,resilience providing technical support, ensuring customer satisfaction. Continuously engaging in innovative tech industry trends to effectively engage with tech-savvy individuals..

Work Experience

Office Administrator: Quasi Serviced Offices - October 2018 to Date

- Managing communications to customer inquiries through responding to calls, emails, social media platforms-facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn-Whatsapp- and one on one meetings to provide information on workspace solutions and services offered.
- Induct new members and ensure smooth registration on the workspace system improving onboarding efficiency by 98%.
- Setting up office systems such as contract renewals, record and track payments and ensuring an established workflow accuracy
- Assist in planning and launching workspace community events to create community growth and foster relationships and a sense of inclusivity between different members.
- Monitoring customer feedback and engaging prospects by following up with customers to identify areas to improve.
- Developed and continuously monitoring the serviced office website, updating content and ensuring the website is secure. This resulted in a 30% increase in website traffic within the first three months post-launch.
- Collaborating with marketing team to develop and execute promotional campaigns and monthly newsletters, to increase client acquisition

Help Desk Support

 Resolving issues and troubleshooting technical problems such as network, hardware and software issues.

I.T. Intern: Bizone Printing and Packaging Limited - Sept 2016 to Dec 2016

- Assisted in hardware, software installation and maintenance.
- Managed infrastructure administration activities such as server and storage capacity and directory services management.
- Configured and managed backup and restoration procedures, IP routing, switching, subnetting and network management.
- Ensuring Servers, Switches, LAN cables, laying cables and other systems are working in good condition.

Kev Achievements

- Analyzed system requirements and created an automated data backup to increase system efficiency.
- Assisted I.T. manager in administration applications reducing 20% workload.

Education

Diploma in Information Technology -Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture & Technology (J.K.U.A.T.) - 2015-2017

High School Certificate- KSCE - Mahiga Girls Secondary School - 2011 to 2014

Skills

- Customer service,
- Organizational Skills
- Problem -solving
- Excellent written and verbal communication (English Language)
- Flexible and Adaptable
- Team work

Technical

- Proficiency in web development (Html, CSS, JavaScript)
- Network Configuration, IT Support and Troubleshooting
- Proficiency in microsoft technologies, google suite, Adobe creative tools.